https://www.whoson.com/privacy/

You’ve hit the policy area of the WhosOn website.Here, you can read up on our privacy policy and learn more about how we use and process data.Non-personal informationIn general, you can visit Parker Software on the web without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. Our web servers collect the domain names, not the email addresses, of visitors.We may also collect and store other information about your visit on an anonymous, aggregate basis. This information may include the time and length of your visit, the pages you look at on our sites, and the site you visited just before coming to ours. We may record the name of your internet service provider, browser type, and country of origin. We use this information only to measure site activity and to develop ideas for improving our sites. Personal informationFor the purposes of this privacy policy, personal information is any information about an identifiable and/or identified individual, other than the person’s business title or business contact information, when used or disclosed for the purpose of business communications.Personal information does not include anonymous or non-personal information (i.e., information that cannot be associated with or tracked back to a specific individual). What personal information do we collect?•Name• Email address• Postal address• Telephone numberIn addition to the above, personal information may also include any information provided to Parker Software through email, telephone, live chat or other communication methods, which is voluntarily disclosed during communication with Parker Software.As a general rule, Parker Software collects personal information directly from you. Where the personal information that we collect about you is held by a third party, we will obtain your permission before we seek out this information from such sources.cParker Software will only collect, process or use personal information as far as is permitted or instructed by applicable law or regulatory requirements. Where permitted or required by applicable law or regulatory requirements, we may collect information about you without your knowledge or consent.   Why do we collect personal information?This information is collected for the purpose of establishing, managing or maintaining a contract or business relationship with Parker Software. Such uses include:• For the delivery of newsletter services• To provision and provide service(s) as provided by Parker Software• Delivery of contractual obligations “Consent” is used as a legal basis for Marketing campaigns not covered by a legitimate interest“Legitimate interest” is also utilised on a case by case basis for marketing campaigns. Legitimate interest assessments are performed for each campaign performed under the legal basis. Details of this assessment can be requested per campaign How do we use your personal information?We may use your personal information for the purposes described in this privacy policy; or for any additional purposes that we advise you of and, where your consent is required by law, we have obtained your consent in respect of the use or disclosure of your personal information.We may use your personal information without your knowledge or consent where we are permitted or required by applicable law or regulatory requirements to do so. When do we disclose your personal information?In consideration of local legislation, we may share your personal information with our employees, contractors, consultants and other parties who require such information, to the extent necessary for them, to assist us with establishing, managing and maintaining our relationship with you. Personal information is only transferred by us to another country, including within the Parker Software businesses, if this is required or permitted under the applicable data protection law, in particular, only in as far as a reasonable level of data protection is guaranteed in the recipient country.Insofar, we may share personal information with such parties both in and outside of your home jurisdiction, and as a result, your personal information may be collected, used, processed, stored or disclosed in the United Kingdom or United States of America, and in some cases, other countries. If imposed by the applicable law or regulatory requirements, the collecting, use, processing, storage or disclosing and transferring, will only take place after obtaining the required permission by the respective authorities.When we share personal information with such parties we typically require that they only use or disclose such personal information in a manner consistent with the use and disclosure provisions of this privacy policy.In addition, personal information may be disclosed or transferred to another party (including to another member of the Parker Software businesses outside of your home jurisdiction) in the event of a change in ownership of, or a grant of a security interest in, all or a part of Parker Software through, for example, an asset or share sale, or some other form of business combination, merger or joint venture, to the extent that such disclosure or transfer of personal information is required to complete the transaction and is permitted by the applicable data protection laws, and provided that such party is bound by appropriate agreements or obligations and required to use or disclose your personal information in a manner consistent with the use and disclosure provisions of this privacy policy, unless you consent otherwise.Further, your personal information may be disclosed:• As permitted or required by applicable law or regulatory requirements. In such a case, we will endeavour to not disclose more personal information than is required under the circumstances;• To comply with valid legal processes such as search warrants, subpoenas or court orders;• During emergency situations or where necessary to protect the safety of a person or group of persons; or• With your consent where such consent is required by law.We will only disclose personal information insofar as is permitted or required by applicable law or regulatory requirements. In any case, we will not disclose more personal information than is required under the circumstances.   Notification and consentPrivacy laws do not generally require Parker Software to obtain your consent for the collection, use or disclosure of personal information for the purpose of establishing, managing or maintaining a contract. In addition, we may collect, use or disclose your personal information without your knowledge or consent where we are permitted or required by applicable law or regulatory requirements to do so.To the extent that your consent is required, we will obtain a positive indication from you that you consent to Parker Software collecting, using and disclosing your personal information for the purposes stated above (including any other purposes stated or reasonably implied at the time such personal information was provided to us).Where your consent was required for our collection, use or disclosure of your personal information, you may, at any time, withdraw your consent. All communications with respect to such withdrawal or variation of consent should be in writing. How is your personal information protected?Parker Software will maintain physical, technical and procedural safeguards that are appropriate to the sensitivity of the personal information in question. These safeguards are designed to protect your personal information from loss and unauthorized access, copying, use, modification or disclosure.   How long is your personal information retained?Except as otherwise permitted or required by applicable law or regulatory requirements, Parker Software endeavours to retain your personal information only for as long as it believes is necessary to fulfil the purposes for which the personal information was collected (including, for the purpose of meeting any legal, accounting or other reporting requirements or obligations). After this period has passed your personal information will be removed within 1 year, except if law authorizes, expressly or explicitly, a longer period or prescribes a shorter period. If destroying or erasing your personal information is not mandatory by law, we may make it anonymous such that it cannot be associated with or tracked back to you.   Updating your personal informationIt is important that the information contained in our records is both accurate and current. If your personal information happens to change during the course of your relationship with Parker Software, please keep us informed of such changes.   Access to your personal informationYou can ask to see the personal information that we hold about you. If you want to review, verify or correct your personal information, please contact the security team using the contact information set out below. Please note that any such communication must be in writing.When requesting access to your personal information, please note that we may request specific information from you to enable us to confirm your identity and right to access, as well as to search for and provide you with the personal information that we hold about you. Except if forbidden by the applicable law or regulatory requirements, we may charge you a fee to access your personal information; however, we will advise you of any fee in advance. If you require assistance in preparing your request, please contact the security team.Your right to access the personal information that we hold about you is, in principle, absolute. However, there are instances where applicable law or regulatory requirements allow or require us to refuse to provide some or all of the personal information that we hold about you. If your personal information has been destroyed, erased or made anonymous in accordance with our record retention obligations and practices, your right to access your personal information may be restrained.In the event that we cannot provide you with access to your personal information, we will endeavour to inform you of the reasons why, subject to any legal or regulatory restrictions. Privacy ShieldWe adhere to the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework (collectively the “Privacy Shield”) as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use and retention of personal information from the EEA. Parker Software Inc. (“Parker Software”, “Us”, “Our” or “We”) commits to apply the Privacy Shield Principles to all personal information received in the United States from the EEA in reliance on the Privacy Shield.For purposes of enforcing compliance with the Privacy Shield, We are subject to the investigatory and enforcement authority of the Federal Trade Commission (FTC).Under certain conditions detailed in the Privacy Shield, Data Subjects may be able to invoke binding arbitration before the Privacy Shield Arbitration Panel to be created by the U.S. Department of Commerce and the European Commission.For more information about the Privacy Shield, and to view Our certification on the Privacy Shield List, please see the U.S. Department of Commerce’s Privacy Shield website at: https://www.privacyshield.gov.In the context of an onward transfer, a Privacy Shield organization has responsibility for the processing of personal information it receives under the Privacy Shield and subsequently transfers to a third party acting as an agent on its behalf.
The Privacy Shield organization shall remain liable under the Principles if its agent processes such personal information in a manner inconsistent with the Principles, unless the organization proves that it is not responsible for the event giving rise to the damage. Cookies“Cookies” are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifying information. They only contain a secure identifying code that we use to match you to your personal information whenever you return to our site. Your personal information is never directly connected to nor stored on your computer, but is accessed when we identify your cookie to provide you with a more personalised experience when visiting our site.NameDescription_ga _gid _gat_UA_27503741-1These cookies are used to collect information about how visitors use our website. We use the information to compile reports and to help us improve the website. The cookies collect information in an anonymous form, including the number of visitors to the website, where visitors have come to the website from and the pages they visited. MORE INFORMATION OPT OUT_atuvc _atuvsThe AddThis cookie is associated with the ‘share this page’ function, where a user can email or share a link. MORE INFORMATION OPT OUTcookie_notice_acceptedWe issue this cookie when our cookie policy has been accepted.whosonThis cookie is issued by the WhosOn live chat application. It’s used to link a visitor to a ‘visitor record’ which stores the IP address and UserAgent. If you use our live chatWe use Parker Software’s WhosOn product to supply live chat, which we use to handle customer enquiries in real time.We will collect your given name, company name (optional), email address (optional) and the contents of your live chat session. This information will be retained for a maximum of 7 years and will not be shared with any other organisation.You can receive a copy of your chat transcript if you provide your e-mail address at the end of the session. Inquiries or concerns?If you have any questions about this privacy policy or concerns about how we manage your personal information, please contact the security team by telephone, in writing or by email. We will endeavour to answer your questions and advise you of any steps taken to address the issues raised by you. If you are unsatisfied with our response, you may be entitled to make a written submission to the Privacy Commissioner applicable for your jurisdiction.In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, Parker Software commits to resolve complaints about our collection or use of your personal information.
EU individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding our Privacy Shield policy should first contact Parker Software with the details provided under the section “Security team” below.Parker Software has further committed to cooperate with the panel established by the EU data protection authorities (DPAs) with regard to unresolved Privacy Shield complaints concerning data transferred from the EU. Security teamThe security team will oversee compliance with this privacy policy. The contact information for the security team is as follows:(+44) 1782 822 5771-800-680-7712 US Toll Freesecurity@parkersoftware.com Revisions to this privacy policyParker Software may occasionally make changes to this privacy policy to reflect changes in its legal or regulatory obligations, or in the manner in which we deal with your personal information. We will communicate any revised version of this privacy policy. Any changes to this privacy policy will be effective from the time they are communicated, provided that any change that relates to why we collect, use or disclose your personal information will not apply to you, where your consent is required to such collection, use or disclosure, until we have obtained your consent to such change.This privacy policy was last reviewed on 28th March 2018. Interpretation of this privacy policyAny interpretation associated with this privacy policy will be made by the security team. This privacy policy includes examples but is not intended to be restricted in its application to such examples, therefore where the word ‘including’ is used, it shall mean ‘including without limitation’.This privacy policy does not create or confer upon any individual any rights, or impose upon Parker Software any rights or obligations outside of, or in addition to, any rights or obligations imposed by the privacy laws applicable to such individual’s personal information. Should there be, in a specific case, any inconsistency between this privacy policy and such privacy laws, this privacy policy shall be interpreted, in respect of that case, to give effect to, and comply with, such privacy laws.
We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. If you continue to use this site we will assume that you are happy with it.Accept
